<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>Arxiv news</title><link>https://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveRss</link><description>This is a description.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/MV.jpg</url><title>Arxiv news</title><link>https://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveRss</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 01:33:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><itunes:category text="Technology"><itunes:category text="Podcasting"/></itunes:category><item><title>On-chip broadband plasmon-induced transparency based on plasmonic metal-insulator-metal waveguides. </title><description>Title: On-chip broadband plasmon-induced transparency based on plasmonic metal-insulator-metal waveguides.   Abstract: As an analogue of electromagnetically induced transparency (EIT), plasmon-induced transparency (PIT) has been realized both in plasmonic metamaterial and waveguide structures. Via near-field coupling within unit cells, PIT with broadband could be produced by plasmonic metamaterials, which, however, has not been realized in on-chip plasmonic waveguide structures. Here, we introduce broadband PIT based on a plasmonic metal-insulator-metal (MIM) waveguide system. Utilizing the direct coupling structure, PIT emerges based on an easy-fabricated structure without gap. By tuning coupling distance, the transparent window can be continuously tuned from narrow- to broadband. Such device is promising for on-chip applications on sensing, filtering and slow light over a broad frequency range.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A4.mp3</guid><enclosure url="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A4.mp3" length="265536" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:image href="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A4.jpg"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit></item><item><title>Enhancing keV high harmonic signals generated by long-wave infrared lasers. </title><description>Title: Enhancing keV high harmonic signals generated by long-wave infrared lasers.   Abstract: It is demonstrated by single-atom simulations that X-ray signals in the 3.4 to 4 keV region from an 8 micron laser driven high harmonic generation can be increased by more than two orders of magnitude when a single-cycle pulse centered at 800 nm is added. The ionization probability of a helium atom by the two-pulse field is set to 4.56x10^-5, which is needed for balancing the index of refraction of free electrons with that of neutral helium atoms to achieve phase matching.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A3.mp3</guid><enclosure url="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A3.mp3" length="177696" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:image href="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A3.jpg"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit></item><item><title>High-efficiency three-party quantum key agreement protocol with quantum dense coding and Bell states. </title><description>Title: High-efficiency three-party quantum key agreement protocol with quantum dense coding and Bell states.   Abstract: We propose a high-efficiency three-party quantum key agreement protocol, by utilizing two-photon polarization-entangled Bell states and a few single-photon polarization states as the information carriers, and we use the quantum dense coding method to improve its efficiency. In this protocol, each participant performs one of four unitary operations to encode their sub-secret key on the passing photons which contain two parts, the first quantum qubits of Bell states and a small number of single-photon states. At the end of this protocol, based on very little information announced by other, all participants involved can deduce the same final shared key simultaneously. We analyze the security and the efficiency of this protocol, showing that it has a high efficiency and can resist both outside attacks and inside attacks. As a consequence, our protocol is a secure and efficient three-party quantum key agreement protocol.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A2.mp3</guid><enclosure url="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A2.mp3" length="292704" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:image href="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A2.jpg"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit></item><item><title>Generalized Brewster-angle effect in thin-film optical absorbers and its application for graphene hydrogen sensing. </title><description>Title: Generalized Brewster-angle effect in thin-film optical absorbers and its application for graphene hydrogen sensing.   Abstract: Generalized Brewster angle (GBA) is the incidence angle at which polarization by reflection for p- and s-polarized light takes place. Realizing s-polarization Brewster effect requires a material with magnetic response which is challenging at optical frequencies since the magnetic response of materials at these frequencies is extremely weak. Here, we experimentally realize GBA effect in the visible using a thin-film absorber system consisting of a dielectric film on an absorbing substrate. Polarization by reflection is realized for both p- and s- polarized light at different angles of incidence and multiple wavelengths. We provide a theoretical framework for the generalized Brewster effect in thin-film light absorbers. We demonstrate hydrogen gas sensing using a single layer graphene film transferred on a thin-film absorber at the GBA with ~1 fg/mm2 aerial mass sensitivity. The ultrahigh sensitivity stems from the strong phase sensitivity near point of darkness, particularly at the GBA, and the strong light-matter interaction in planar nanocavities. These findings depart from the traditional domain of thin-films as mere interference optical coatings and highlight its many potential applications including gas sensing and biosensing.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A1.mp3</guid><enclosure url="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A1.mp3" length="412608" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:image href="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A1.jpg"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit></item><item><title>Plasmonics Theory for Biosensor Design: Mathematical Formulations and Practical Applications. </title><description>Title: Plasmonics Theory for Biosensor Design: Mathematical Formulations and Practical Applications.   Abstract: The last two decades have witnessed an exponential growth and tremendous developments in wireless technologies and systems, and their associated applications. In the recent years following 2006, there has been a great surge in interest in the newly emerging plasmonics nanotechnology because this new device technology provides tremendous synergy between electronic and photonic devices. Electronics devices are down-scalable up to the nanoscale size but have limited processor speed due to thermal and signal delay issues associated with electronic devices. On the other hand, photonic devices have extremely high speed and high data carrying capacity but are limited in size to the diffraction law such that the size of a photonic device should be equal to about half of its operational wavelength. The size mismatch between electronic devices and photonic devices inhibits the advantageous interfacing between these two device technologies and here plasmonics nanotechnology plays the important role of interfacing these two technologies. Plasmonics technology provides high speed interconnections with high data carrying capacity between nano-scale electronic devices opening a new field of research which is on-chip high speed nano-networks [28]. It is this great advantage of plasmonics technology that made it a very interesting technology for implementation for the design of a miniature real-time biosensor. In our plasmonic biosensor design, we utilized a subset of plasmonics technology which is surface plasmon wave generation in order to continuously monitor the concentration of a desired analyte.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A0.mp3</guid><enclosure url="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A0.mp3" length="508032" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:image href="http://engn1931z29.pythonanywhere.com/serveFile/A0.jpg"/><itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit></item></channel></rss>